=Deity Of Love= =Episode 22=
= إله الحب = = الحلقة 22 =
Xiaoqing.
شياو تشينغ.
I'm still a demon.
ما زلت شيطان.
I can't become a human being.
لا أستطيع أن أصبح إنسانًا.
I've figured it out.
لقد اكتشفت ذلك.
Being a demon or not
كونك شيطان أم لا
can't be decided by anyone.
لا يمكن أن يقرره أي شخص.
Then why Demon Hunters
ثم لماذا صائدو الشياطين
keep catching and killing demons?
استمر في اصطياد الشياطين وقتلها؟
There are good men and bad men in the world.
هناك رجال طيبون وأشرار في العالم.
It is the same with the demon.
نفس الشيء مع الشيطان.
Xiaoqing is the good demon.
شياو تشينغ هو الشيطان الجيد.
But being with a demon
لكن كونك مع شيطان
is not allowed by the public.
غير مسموح به من قبل الجمهور.
Even if people don't allow it,
حتى لو لم يسمح الناس بذلك ،
I will always stand by you.
سأقف بجانبك دائما.
A demon is coming!
شيطان قادم!
Ahhh!
أهه!
There's a demon!
هناك شيطان!
Help!
مساعدة!
Miss Xiaoqing, don't be afraid.
آنسة شياو تشينغ ، لا تخافي.
If there's another demon,
إذا كان هناك شيطان آخر ،
I will protect you.
سأحميك.
How did you meet this demon?
كيف قابلت هذا الشيطان؟
It's not difficult to meet her.
ليس من الصعب مقابلتها.
She's on the streets and
انها في الشوارع و
killing Demon Hunters now.
قتل صيادي الشياطين الآن.
Especially me.
خصوصا أنا.
The handsome talent.
الموهبة الوسيم.
(This demon was killed by
(قُتل هذا الشيطان على يد
Ling Zhao.)
لينغ تشاو.)
You've just recovered.
لقد تعافيت للتو.
Where are you going to?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب ل؟
Now the demon is raging,
الآن الشيطان يحتدم ،
so I'm going to the Soul Department
لذلك أنا ذاهب إلى قسم الروح
to kill the demon.
لقتل الشيطان.
Then I will go with you.
ثم سأذهب معك.
You'd better stay here.
من الأفضل لك البقاء هنا.
It's too dangerous outside.
إنه أمر خطير للغاية بالخارج.
I heard that
سمعت ان
you want to work for the Soul Department?
تريد العمل في قسم الروح؟
Recently, a demon killed many Demon Hunters.
في الآونة الأخيرة ، قتل شيطان العديد من صيادي الشياطين.
I also want to help and catch the demon.
أريد أيضًا أن أساعد وأمسك بالشيطان.
Oh?
أوه؟
Really?
هل حقا؟
Because I may know something
لأنني قد أعرف شيئًا
about that demon.
عن هذا الشيطان.
It's great for you to have this ambition.
إنه لأمر رائع أن يكون لديك هذا الطموح.
However,
لكن،
what makes you think that
ما الذي يجعلك تظن ذلك
we need you to work for us?
نريدك للعمل معنا؟
I wonder whether Your Excellency knows
أتساءل عما إذا كان صاحب السعادة يعلم
which demon is killing Demon Hunters now?
أي شيطان يقتل صيادي الشياطين الآن؟
The demon is ever-changing.
الشيطان دائم التغير.
There's no need for me to remember all of them.
لا داعي لتذكرهم جميعًا.
I understood it now.
فهمت ذلك الآن.
My Lord,
ربي،
he seems to suspect you.
يبدو أنه يشك فيك.
Then kill him.
ثم اقتله.
Kill him legally.
اقتله قانونيا.
Department Head,
رئيس القسم،
Ning Yu from Qingyun Valley comes.
يأتي نينغ يو من وادي تشينغيون.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Ning Yu is willing to join the Soul Department.
نينغ يو على استعداد للانضمام إلى قسم الروح.
Hope you can give me a chance.
أتمنى أن تعطيني فرصة.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
As long as you pass the test,
طالما نجحت في الاختبار ،
you can be the member of
يمكنك أن تكون عضوا في
our Soul Department.
قسم الروح لدينا.
What's the test?
ما هو الاختبار؟
There is someone who is harboring demons.
هناك شخص يؤوي الشياطين.
I need you to bring him here.
أريدك أن تحضره إلى هنا.
Yes.
نعم.
(Why does Ling Zhao also have the Heart Lock Seal?)
(لماذا تمتلك Ling Zhao أيضًا ختم قفل القلب؟)
You look different.
أنت تبدو مختلفة.
Because I have figured out something.
لأنني اكتشفت شيئًا.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
I will never let you go.
أنا لن اترك ابدا تغادر.
Xiaoqing,
شياو تشينغ ،
I love you.
أحبك.
Are you willing to be with me forever?
هل أنت على استعداد لتكون معي إلى الأبد؟
Yes, I am.
نعم أنا.
Xiuning?
شيونينغ؟
The Heart Lock Seal.
ختم قفل القلب.
Oh no.
أوه لا.
(I'll obtain the power of the Heart Lock Seal soon.)
(سأحصل على قوة ختم Heart Lock قريبًا.)
Stay away from me.
ابق بعيد عني.
I might hurt you.
قد أؤذيك.
It works.
إنها تعمل.
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
Why this jade
لماذا هذا اليشم
can ease the pain brought by the seal?
هل يمكن أن يخفف الألم الذي يجلبه الختم؟
If the jade can ease your pain,
إذا كان اليشم يمكن أن يخفف من ألمك ،
I'll stay with you forever.
سأبقى معك إلى الأبد.
I remembered that you said
تذكرت ما قلته
only your master can strengthen the seal.
فقط سيدك يمكنه تقوية الختم.
But...
ولكن...
Let's go back to Qingyun Valley.
دعنا نعود إلى وادي تشينغيون.
No, we can't.
لا ، لا نستطيع.
Aren't you going to prove my innocence?
ألن تثبت براءتي؟
How can you prove it if I don't go back?
كيف يمكنك إثبات ذلك إذا لم أعود؟
Let's go.
لنذهب.
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.) (Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)
(حق إعادة بث المسرحية على الإنترنت ملك لي.) (شركة Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co.، Ltd.)